let baseDePreguntas = [
  {
    pregunta: "My father __________ (go) to work by car yesterday.",
    respuesta: "went",
    distractores: ["goed", "gone", "goes"],
  },
  {
    pregunta: "It ____ snow a lot in Canada.",
    respuesta: "did not",
    distractores: ["do not", "will not", "did"],
  },
  {
    pregunta: "Did they ____ a good time?.",
    respuesta: "have",
    distractores: ["haven't", "has", "had"],
  },
  {
    pregunta: "Did your mother ever ____ a novel?.",
    respuesta: "watch",
    distractores: ["watches", "watching", "watchn't"],
  },
  {
    pregunta: "My brother _____(help) me with my homework. ",
    respuesta: "helped",
    distractores: ["helps", "help", "helping"],
  },
  {
    pregunta: "Forma negativa de: I studied at Concordia University, in Montreal.",
    respuesta: "I did not study at Concordia University, in Montreal.",
    distractores: ["I not study at Concordia University, in Montreal.", "I did not studied at Concordia University, in Montreal.", "I not studied at Concordia University, in Montreal."],
  },
  {
    pregunta: "My father never ____(play) football when he was a child.",
    respuesta: "played",
    distractores: ["plays", "playing", "player"],
  },
  {
    pregunta: "She ____(be) very nice.",
    respuesta: "wasn't",
    distractores: ["weren't", "wasnot", "didn't"],
  },
  {
    pregunta: "Where ____ last Friday.",
    respuesta: "did you go",
    distractores: ["you goes", "you not go", "you gon't"],
  },
  {
    pregunta: " Where ____ last Friday?",
    respuesta: "did you go",
    distractores: ["you went", "you go", "did go you"],
  },
  {
    pregunta: "Forma negativa de: The boys took off the mudguards of their bicycles.",
    respuesta: "The boys did not take off the mudguards of their bicycles.",
    distractores: ["The boys not didn't take off the mudguards of their bicycles.", "The boys do not take off the mudguards of their bicycles.", "The boys not take off the mudguards of their bicycles."],
  },
  {
    pregunta: "We ____(write) our letters.",
    respuesta: "wrote",
    distractores: ["written", "writes", "writing"],
  },
  {
    pregunta: "She _____(have) five children.",
    respuesta: "had",
    distractores: ["has", "have", "haved"],
  },
  {
    pregunta: "Andrea ____ go to the cinema three times last week.",
    respuesta: "didn't",
    distractores: ["do not", "was not", "did"],
  },
  {
    pregunta: " How many books last summer?",
    respuesta: "did you read",
    distractores: ["you read", "you did read", "did you readed"],
  },
];